#### Introduction

Nikhil S

Intro:

Keen business professional with expertise in Branding and Strategy; Master's in business Administration from IIM Ahmedabad (IIMA)

Role Heading:

Strategy & Growth

# Introductory Paragraph:

Nikhil is a keen business professional with a Master's in Business Administration from IIM Ahmedabad (IIMA), specializing in Branding and Strategy. He possesses a diverse skill set, including Business Development, Data Analytics, Strategy & Growth, and Branding Solutions. Nikhil has completed certifications in User Experience (UI/UX) Design and Agile Project Management from Google, enhancing his expertise in user-centered design and agile methodologies. His proficiency in Corporate Finance encompasses budgeting, pre-due diligence, and pitch deck reports.

Currently, Nikhil holds a strategic role in the CEO's Office at Pack8 in Mumbai, focusing on Strategy and Growth. His previous experience includes a significant tenure at Amul.

Full Name: Nikhil Shelke

Age: 28 Years

Language: English, Hindi, Marathi, Sanskrit.

Phone Number: 9561280118

Email: a19nikhils@gmail.com

Address: Pune, Maharashtra, India.

#### Skills

#### 1. Business Development

Data Analytics, Strategy & Growth, Branding Solutions

#### 2. User Experience (UI/UX) Design by Google

User-centered design, ideate solutions, wireframes and prototypes, test and iterate on designs.

# 3. Agile Project Management by Google

Agile project management approach and philosophy, Scrum framework.

## 4. Corporate Finance

Budgeting, Pre-due Diligence & Pitch Deck Reports.

Education:

June 2019- June 2021

MBA from Indian Institute of Management, Ahmedabad

MBA Grades: 3.04/4.33

June 2014- June 2018

B.Tech (Food) from Dr.ASCAET, MPKV, Rahuri, Maharashtra

Engg Grades: 8.58/10 [IR 3 & 2nd in Department]

June 2012- March 2014

HSC: 80.63% | Laxmanrao Aapte Junior College, Pune, Maharashtra.

SSC: 94.60% | Malojiraje Vidyalaya, Lonand, Satara, Maharashtra.

## Experience:

1. CEO's Office, Strategy and Growth

Pack8 (Officedeck Technologies Pvt Ltd) Mumbai, India

June 2023 to Present

Developed OKR's & KPIs for MarComm, Sales, & Operations Depts. driving accountability & performance; Performed gap analysis & designed E-commerce; Prepared investors pitch deck reports; **Liaised** between firm, developer & web-designer for Order Management System & new **Website** development.

2. Amul (GCMMF), Mumbai, India

Sales & Marketing Professional

June 2021 to April 2022

Spearheaded sales tasks of branch Generating 4.5 Cr monthly Revenue; Utilized BI, SAP and Core Stocky apps for efficient monitoring of sales, stocks & other growth parameters; Indented production management with 4 Union Plants; dealt with 22 distributors via daily coordination for product orders.

3. Summer Internship Marketing Research

Amul (GCMMF), Mumbai, India

*April 2020 to June 2020* 

Studied changing behaviour of millennials for milk-based beverages viz-à-viz carbonated drinks & juices; Evaluated product attributes & lead qualitative research on \$5.3 Bn Indian milk-based beverage industry; Identified, evaluated & reviewed factors impacting consumer behaviour of millennials in Mumbai region.

#### Cerificates:

- 1. Certified by Google for UX/UI User Experience Design
- 2. Certified by Google for Agile Project Management.
- 3. Certified by Google in Digital Marketing & Data Analytics.
- 4. Certified by Udemy in MS Excel Advanced.

### Change My Projects to My Activities

- 1. Positions of Responsibilities
- 2. Scholastic Achievements
- 3. Academic Projects
- 4. Extracurricular Activities
- 5. All

## Positions of Responsibilities

1. Coordinator Stargazers (The Astronomy Club of IIMA)

Feb 2020-January 2021

Recruited & led 40 members team; organized quizzes, created blogposts; Ideated & initiated creation of Monthly Magazine Voyager garnering 4.95K+ impressions for its 3 issues.

2. Sports Secretary (SAC), Undergrad Institute

March 2017-February 2018

Organized total 12 games for 225+ students in the Annual Sports Week and handled a budget of Rs.45K.

3. Movies & Design Club (MAD), IIM Ahmedabad

September 2019 – March 2021

Co-produced Welcome Video for new batch; solely designed thumbnail having 150K+ YouTube views; Generated revenue of Rs.15,000 for the MAD club being part of the Digital Design Team of Finomena.

4. Cultural Event Head, Ganeshotsav, Undergrad Institute July August 2016 to August 2017

Coordinated with 230+ students for the Ganeshotsav; 1/240 elected and handled budget of Rs.4.5 lakh

#### Scholastic Achievements

1. IIMA SNBS Scholarship

Received SNBS Scholarship from IIMA of worth Rs.1.5 Lakh via maintaining required academic CGPA.

#### 2. GATE Exam & SSC Board

Secured AIR 283 in GATE'19 exam; Ranked 1/154 in school for SSC board with 90+ in 5/6 subjects

# 3. Class Representative

1/3 selected among 64 students of the B. Tech. Class of 2014 for 3 consecutive years.

# **Academic Projects**

- 1. Nutrition Bars Strategy Project
  - Analysed value chain for Business Expansion Strategies for major players in Nutritional Bars segment.
  - b. Prepared Go to Market strategy for Nutrition Bars segment; Surveyed 90+ resp. & conducted 5+ FGDs.

## 2. Sahyadri Farms Web User Research

- a. Performed in-depth user research to evaluate expected features & parameters on Sahyadri Retail website.
- b. Benchmarked 12+ cumulative usability heuristics and parameters to track live use of B2C Retail websites.

## 3. Gokul Milk Coop.

a. Analysed procurement, processing of 7 lakh litre milk per day; conducted a market survey & studied QC.

# 4. Project (Food & Process Engg)

- a. Conducted the study and investigated the Storage Behaviour of Pomegranate (Punica Granatum L.) Juice
- b. Prepared & tested Juice for TSS, pH, Antioxidant Activity & optimized the final product over 90 days

#### **Extracurricular Activities**

- 1. National Cadet Corps (NCC)
  - a. Awarded NCC A, B, C certificates with AAA Grade; actively participated in two Annual Training Camps
  - b. 1/10 selected among 270 cadets as the Best Cadet with a work of 100+ hrs & active interest in Sports
- 2. Table Tennis: Gold Medallist
  - a. Captained Gold Medallist team in Intercollegiate TT Tournament with 40+ participating college teams
  - b. Represented in the West-zonal Games as the University Captain of TT in Inter-University Tournament
- 3. Shaurya IIMA
  - a. Gold Medallist in TT games Shaurya'19: National level sports tournament with 20+ college participants
- 4. Intercollegiate Chess Captain
  - Captained Intercollegiate Chess Team for consecutive years 2016 & 2017; selected among 240+ students

Hobbies	Graphic Designing	Video Editing	Calligraphy	Swimming
<b>1</b> +91 9423964039	△ Dorm 18 Room 30,	, IIMA <u>in</u> <u>www</u>	v.linkedin.com/in/nikhil-s-8616b0179	
a19nikhils@iima.ac.in	nikhils@iima.ac.in			

## Phone Number:

- 1. 9561280118
- 2. 9423964039